<package>
	<id>me.pr0crustes.betterw</id>
	<name>BetterW</name>
	<version>1.1.8-1</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>10.0.0</miniOS>
			<maxiOS>13.4</maxiOS>
			<otherVersions>unconfirmed</otherVersions>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies></dependencies>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description>
			A bunch of whatsapp features:  
			1 - No Read Receipt, that prevents others from seeing when you read a message, but still allowing you to see when others read yours.  
			2 - Who Is Online, that allows you to see who is online, drawing a green or red circle around their profile picture.  
			2.1 - As Dot, replaces the Who Is Online indicator with a dot. Who Is Online needs to be enabled.  
			3 - Confirm Call, that asks you to confirm your desire to call another user, preventing accidental voice / video calls. Also allow for phone calls.  
			4 - Don't Delete, will make so that when someone deletes a message, it does not delete in your device, adding a alert at the top of the message, alerting that the message was saved from oblivion. There is a know issue where sometimes another message can overlap the deleted one, until the app is restarted.  
			5 - No Delete Limit, removing the time limit to delete a message.  
			6 - Never Online (BETA), disabling your online status. Issue: Currently, it also disables your abillity to see who is online. Ussing it disables Who Is Online.  
			7 - No Typing, not showing when you are typing but still allowing you to see when others are typing.  
			8 - Status Downloader, allowing you to donwload status - just click the ... button when seeing one.  
			9 - Global Support, adds whatsapp support to ipad | ipod. Should be enabled in settings.  
			10 - Delete Subsequents, allowing you to easily revoke a bunch of messages.  
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>	
	<changelog>
		<change>Fixed confirm calls, removed dark mode.</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<name>Source Code</name>
		<url>https://github.com/pr0crustes/BetterW</url>
		
		<name>Reddit</name>
		<url>https://www.reddit.com/user/assembly_programmer</url>

		<name>Twitter</name>
		<url>https://twitter.com/pr0crustes</url>
	</links>
</package>
